Guide to the Records and Papers of Terry Sanford, 1945-1998 UA.03.60.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Series 3. Political Papers, 1965-1976
  - Subseries 3.7. Democratic Charter Commission, 1972-1975., 14.0 ln. ft. (about 12,000 items (Box 212-222)
    The records, though largely unorganized, document Sanford and the Commission's efforts from 1972-1974. Includes folders on individual states, which often contain lists of delegates and material on individual state conferences or hearings (including agendas, discussions, and summaries of proceedings) held to discuss the proposed Charter. Sanford usually attended these state conferences and delivered the opening and/or closing remarks. Other material consists of Commission member lists, questionnaires on party structure and charter proposals, and Commission-related newspaper clippings. The correspondence is not foldered together, but spread throughout the records. Correspondents include President Jimmy Carter, then Governor of Georgia; Robert Strauss, Chairman of the Democratic National Committee; members of the Commission; and Democratic members of Congress.
    Included among the approximately 20 original reel to reel films and audiotapes and 20 audiocassettes are session recordings from Commission conferences (in Colorado, Massachusetts, New Mexico, Oklahoma, Texas, Washington D.C., and Wisconsin); and interviews with members of the Commission for a proposed public relations project in 1974 (not completed). Most films and cassettes are labeled and in fair condition.
- Series 4. Photographs and printed matter, 1945-1986., 4.0 ln. ft. (about 3,000 items (Box 223)
  The photographs and negatives span Sanford's career. Photographs are arranged and foldered by subject, though some subjects are vague (people and political for example). Others include: Duke University Activities, Functions; 1972 Presidential Campaign; FBI; Gubernatorial Years; and University of North Carolina Law School. Among the individuals: Jimmy Carter, Andy Griffith, J. Edgar Hoover, Lyndon B. Johnson, John F. Kennedy, Soviet Premier Kosygin, Carl Sandburg, Strom Thurmond, Harry S. Truman, John Wayne, and Sanford's family and friends. For additional photographs see the general photograph collection in the Duke University Archives.
  The printed matter includes newspaper articles written during his tenure as President of Duke University. A majority of the articles are from the Durham newspapers and the Duke student newspaper, The Chronicle. The articles are poorly organized, though hint at a chronological arrangement. The document box contains ready reference files, again focusing primarily on his tenure at Duke. This includes copies of speeches, clippings on his inauguration, and programs for a tribute ceremony to Sanford in 1985. Other files include the Democratic Charter Commission, U.S. Senate, and other political clippings.
  Could only find one box of photographic materials in January 2007.
- Series 5. Oversize and Artifacts, 14.1 ln. ft. (about 1,000) items (Box 225-229)
  Series contains various artifacts including framed photos, cartoons (Nixon Library cartoon by Dwane Powell, News and Observer, August 16, 1981 Box 229) scrapbooks, photographs, honorary degrees, greetings from other colleges and universities, citations, campaign posters, and President Sanford's doctoral robe and sports jacket.
  The framed photos include:
  Dinner honoring Prof. Joseph J. Spengler, Jan. 1972
  The Eastward Duke University Marine Lab, 1979
  Great Wall of China
  Duke University-Gettysburg Nestorian Expedition in Southeast Turkey, June 1982
- Series 6. Covington/Ellis Book Materials
  This series includes correspondence, diaries, audiotapes, transcript, printed materials, and other personal papers acquired by the authors of Terry Sanford: Politics, Progress, and Outrageous Ambitions (Durham: DU Press, 1999) from Terry Sanford. Subjects include youth, military service and early political career, presidential nomination campaign papers, transcripts of interviews Sanford conducted with his mother, President's appointment book, transcripts of speeches at roasts, Covington-Ellis interviews with Sanford, as well as his friends and acquaintances.
  Many of these materials may have come from and are related to other series in this collection. Some materials are copies of items held by the Duke University Archives and the University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill's Special Collections.
  - Clippings
    - Assorted Clippings, 1983; 1992-1993; 1995 (Box 191)
    - Assorted News Clippings, 1961-1963; 1965 (Box 191)
    - Clippings, 1970-1995; 6 folders (Box 190)
    - Clippings, 1971; 1979; 1985 (Box 191)
    - Mrs. Sanford's Clippings, 1944; 1954; 1964-1966 (Box 191)
  - Duke Diaries
    - 1970s?, circa 1970 (Box 194)
    - Terry Sanford, 1971 May 15 (Box 194)
    - Terry Sanford, 1976 August 20-21 (Box 194)
    - Terry Sanford, 1986 December 16-18 (Box 194)
    - Terry Sanford (research notes), undated (Box 194)
    - Terry Sanford Diary, 1970 March 17-July 30 (Box 194)
    - Terry Sanford etc. (Duke Archives excerpts), 1970 (Box 194)
  - Duke Materials
    - Duke Addresses, Speeches, 1981-1984 (Box 184)
    - Duke Financial, 1982 (Box 185)
    - Duke Materials, 1968-1993 (Box 184)
    - Duke Materials, 1994; undated (Box 185)
    - Duke Retirement, 1985 (Box 185)
    - Duke University Letters, 1971-1972; 1976; 1985; 1996-1997 (Box 184)
    - Duke Years, 1969-1998 (Box 184)
    - Nixon Library Controversy, 1970-1971; 1981 (Box 185)
    - Nixon Library Controversy, 1981 (Box 185)
    - Nixon Library Controversy: Bill Green, 1980; 1991; 1997 (Box 185)
    - Nixon Library Controversy: Duke, 1981 (Box 185)
    - Nixon Library Controversy: Nathans, 1981 (Box 184)
    - Nixon Library Controversy: Witt, 1981 (Box 184)
    - Terry Sanford, 1976-1978 (Box 184)
  - Family and Military Matters
    - Belgian American Association Parachute Combat Project, 1945; 1986; 1988; 1992; 1995 (Box 183)
    - Letters from Mother, 1961-1962; 1982 (Box 183)
    - Military Records, 1942-1996; 2 folders (Box 183)
    - Military Service, 1944-1995 (Box 183)
    - Mrs. Sanford's Other Letters, 1960-1983 (Box 183)
    - Youth, 1940 (Box 183)
  - Oral Histories
    - Autry, George: Transcript, 1995 October 2 (Box 192)
    - Bennet, Bert Tape 1, undated (Box 180, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0065)
    - Bennet, Bert Tape 2, undated (Box 180, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0066)
    - Bennett, Bert: Transcript, 1993 October 27-1997 September 10 (Box 192)
    - Cachran, Bill: Transcript, 1995 May 17 (Box 192)
    - Cannon, Hugh, [1993?] October 18 (Box 182, Audio-cassette UA03600001-MCS-0023)
    - Cannon, Hugh, [1993?] December 15 (Box 182, Audio-cassette UA03600001-MCS-0024)
    - Cannon, Hugh, [1994?] April 25 (Box 182, Audio-cassette UA03600001-MCS-0025)
    - Cannon, Hugh first interview, 1993 August (Box 182, Audio-cassette UA03600001-MCS-0022)
    - Cannon, Hugh: Transcript, 1993 December 16-1994 April 24 (Box 192)
    - Carlton, 1998 27 April (Box 180, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0064)
    - Cochrane, Bill Tape 1, [?] 17 May (Box 180, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0062)
    - Cochrane, Bill Tape 2, [?] 17 May (Box 180, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0063)
    - Cooper, David: Transcript, 1993 (Box 192)
    - Deuries, Walt, 1995 22 September (Box 180, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0060)
    - Drew, Tom: Transcript, 1995 May 10 (Box 192)
    - Ehle, [?] )October 27 (Box 182, Audio-cassette UA03600001-MCS-0028)
    - Ehle, John (Side B), Bert B (Side A), [?] October 27 (Box 182, Audio-cassette UA03600001-MCS-0029)
    - Ehle, John: Transcript, 1993 October 27 (Box 192)
    - Fieldwork Data Worksheets, 1995-1996 (Box 194)
    - Fleishman, Joel (Side 1 Only), 1996 22 March (Box 180, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0061)
    - Fleishman, Joel: Transcript, 1996 March 22 (Box 192)
    - Fraber, Donald (War Years), 1996 16 April (Box 180, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0059)
    - Friday, Bill: Transcript, 1996 February 8 (Box 192)
    - Gergen, David, [?] 29 March (Box 180, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0058)
    - Gergen, David: Transcript, 1996 March 29 (Box 192)
    - Green, Bill, 1997 March 7 (Box 182, Audio-cassette UA03600001-MCS-0032)
    - Green, Bill: Transcript, 1997 December 8 (Box 192)
    - Groves, Harry Reference Copy, 1997 24 January (Box 180, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0069)
    - Groves, Harry: Chapel Hill, NC, 1997 24 January (Box 180, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0057)
    - Guillory, Ferrell: Transcript, 1997 December 9 (Box 192)
    - Herring, 1995 February 10 (Box 182, Audio-cassette UA03600001-MCS-0034)
    - Herring, 1995 February 10 (Box 182, Audio-cassette UA03600001-MCS-0035)
    - Herring, Dallas: His Home Rose Hill, NC Tape 1, 1995 10 February (Box 179, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0055)
    - Herring, Dallas: His Home Rose Hill, NC Tape 2, 1995 10 February (Box 179, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0056)
    - Herring, Dallas: Transcript, 1996 February 10 (Box 192)
    - Hillman, Jennifer: Transcript, 1997 November 21 (Box 192)
    - Houing, John Tape 1, 1995 17 January (Box 179, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0054)
    - Hoving, John: Transcript, 1996 January 17 (Box 192)
    - Huestis, Chuck, undated (Box 179, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0053)
    - Huestis, Chuck: Transcript, 1995 Summer (Box 192)
    - Huestis; Griffith, 1995 May 11 (Box 182, Audio-cassette UA03600001-MCS-0036)
    - Lambeth, Tom, [?] 3 May (Box 179, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0052)
    - Lambeth, Tom: Transcript, 1993 December 30-1995 May 3 (Box 192)
    - Marsinko (War Years, Side B), 1996 1 May (Box 179, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0020)
    - Martin, Joe: Transcript, 1995 March 15 (Box 192)
    - McCachren, Bill Tape 2, 1995 11 April (Box 179, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0050)
    - McCachren, Bill: His Hom[e] H[R]C Tape 1, 1995 11 April (Box 179, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0049)
    - McCachren, Bill: Transcript, 1995 April 11 (Box 192)
    - McCoy, Donald: Transcript, 1993 November 17 (Box 192)
    - McCoy, Mutt, 1995 14 July (Box 179, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0048)
    - McCoy, Reginald "Muff": Transcript, [?] July 14 (Box 192)
    - McCoy; Ragan, 1993 November 17 (Box 182, Audio-cassette UA03600001-MCS-0037)
    - McKay, Martha, 1996 6 March (Box 179, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0047)
    - McKay, Martha: Transcript, 1996 March 6 (Box 192)
    - McMahon, Alex, 1996 2 May (Box 179, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0046)
    - McMahon, Alex #1 (Side 2, Side 3), 1996 11 January (Box 179, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0044)
    - McMahon, Alex #2 (Side 1, Tape 3 Side A [conby?]), 1996 11 January (Box 179, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0045)
    - McMahon, Alex: Transcript, 1996 January 11-1996 May 2 (Box 192)
    - McNair, [1996] June 8 (Box 182, Audio-cassette UA03600001-MCS-0026)
    - McNair (Robert?), 1996 June 8 (Box 182, Audio-cassette UA03600001-MCS-0027)
    - Moore, John Henry, 1995 18 December (Box 179, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0041)
    - Morgan, R., 1995 February 8 (Box 182, Audio-cassette UA03600001-MCS-0033)
    - Morgan, Robert: His Office Lillington, NC, Tape 1, 1995 8 February (Box 179, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0042)
    - Morgan, Robert: His Office Lillington, NC, Tape 2, 1995 8 February (Box 179, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0043)
    - Morgan, Robert: Transcript, 1995 February 8 (Box 192)
    - Newton, C., 1995 12 July (Box 179, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0036)
    - Newton, Clint: Transcript, 1995 July 12 (Box 192)
    - Parker, Roy Tape 1 of 1, 1996 23 April (Box 179, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0040)
    - Phillips, Dickson Early Years Reference Copy (Both Sides), 1995 25 April (Box 180, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0068)
    - Phillips, Dickson: 1:30pm His Office, Early Years, 1995 25 April (Box 179, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0039)
    - Phillips, Dickson: Transcript, 1995 April 25 (Box 192)
    - Poole, Sam, [?] March 15 (Box 182, Audio-cassette UA03600001-MCS-0030)
    - Poole, Sam (Side 1 Only), 1996 3 July (Box 179, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0051)
    - Poole, Sam Reference Copy (Side B Blank), 1996 3 July (Box 180, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0067)
    - Poole, Sam: Transcript, 1994 March 14-1996 June 16 (Box 192)
    - Pritkzer, J. B.: Transcript, 1995 October 11 (Box 192)
    - Pritzger, J. B. Tape 1 of 2, 1995 11 October (Box 179, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0037)
    - Pritzger, J. B. Tape 2 of 2, 1995 11 October (Box 179, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0038)
    - Proctor, Sam: Transcript, 1996 May 1 (Box 193)
    - Proctor, Samuel (Side A) by Phone, 1996 1 May (Box 179, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0020)
    - Ragan, Sam: Transcript, 1993 November 17 (Box 193)
    - Rankin, Ed, [?] 7 December (Box 182, Audio-cassette UA03600001-MCS-0020)
    - Rankin, Ed, [?] 27 January (Box 182, Audio-cassette UA03600001-MCS-0021)
    - Rankin, Ed: Transcript, 1993 December 7-1994 January 27 (Box 193)
    - Reese, Matt Tape 1 of 1, [?] 17 January (Box 179, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0027)
    - Reese, Matt: Transcript, 1996 January 17 (Box 193)
    - Roberts, Gene, 1995 7 October (Box 179, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0019)
    - Rose, Charles Tape #1, [?] 17 January (Box 179, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0028)
    - Rose, Charlie: Transcript, 1996 January 17 (Box 193)
    - Rose, Margarit Tape 1, [?] 7 September (Box 179, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0030)
    - Rose, Margarit Tape 2, [?] 7 September (Box 179, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0031)
    - Rose, Marie Glenn (Sanford): Transcript, 1996 August 15 (Box 193)
    - Rose, Mary Glenn (Sides A and B [?]) Tape 1 of 1, [?] 15 August (Box 179, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0029)
    - Sanders, John: Transcript, 1996 April 8 (Box 193)
    - Sanford, Betsee: Transcript, 1996 April 24 (Box 193)
    - Sanford, Helen and Mary Tape 2, 1995 24 June (Box 179, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0026)
    - Sanford, Helen and Mary, starts with Helen --- and Mary Sanford Tape 1, 1995 24 June (Box 179, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0025)
    - Sanford, Helen and Mary: Transcript, 1995 June 24 (Box 193)
    - Sanford, Margaret Rose: Transcript, 1995 September 7 (Box 193)
    - Sanford, Terry, 1998 24 March (Box 179, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0001)
    - Sanford, Terry, [1993] 29 December (Box 182, Audio-cassette UA03600001-MCS-0008)
    - Sanford, Terry, 1993 14 January (Box 182, Audio-cassette UA03600001-MCS-0001)
    - Sanford, Terry, 1993 16 November (Box 182, Audio-cassette UA03600001-MCS-0007)
    - Sanford, Terry, 1993 27 January (Box 182, Audio-cassette UA03600001-MCS-0003)
    - Sanford, Terry, 1994 1 February (Box 182, Audio-cassette UA03600001-MCS-0010)
    - Sanford, Terry, 1994 1 February (Box 182, Audio-cassette UA03600001-MCS-0011)
    - Sanford, Terry, 1994 15 March (Box 182, Audio-cassette UA03600001-MCS-0014)
    - Sanford, Terry, 1994 15 March (Box 182, Audio-cassette UA03600001-MCS-0015)
    - Sanford, Terry, 1994 20 April (Box 182, Audio-cassette UA03600001-MCS-0018)
    - Sanford, Terry #2, 1997 27 June (Box 179, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0003)
    - Sanford, Terry (Side 1 of 3, Side 2 of 3) Tape #1, 1995 20 December (Box 179, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0010)
    - Sanford, Terry (Side A 10/5, Side B 11/16, 1993 5 October; 16 November (Box 182, Audio-cassette UA03600001-MCS-0006)
    - Sanford, Terry (Side A 12/29, Side B 12/30), 1993 29-30 December (Box 182, Audio-cassette UA03600001-MCS-0009)
    - Sanford, Terry (Side B Blank), 1993 14 January (Box 182, Audio-cassette UA03600001-MCS-0002)
    - Sanford, Terry 1/27 short, 8/18 [balance?] of A and all of B, 1993 27 January; 18 August (Box 182, Audio-cassette UA03600001-MCS-0004)
    - Sanford, Terry 2/9, 1994 9 February (Box 182, Audio-cassette UA03600001-MCS-0013)
    - Sanford, Terry 2/9 Tape 1, 1994 9 February (Box 182, Audio-cassette UA03600001-MCS-0012)
    - Sanford, Terry 3/17 [?] 3/16/95 - [?], 1995 16 March (Box 182, Audio-cassette UA03600001-MCS-0016)
    - Sanford, Terry 8/18, 10/5 (Side A 8/18, Side B 8/18), 1993 18 August (Box 182, Audio-cassette UA03600001-MCS-0005)
    - Sanford, Terry and [hiboy?], LBURG, 1995 17 March (Box 182, Audio-cassette UA03600001-MCS-0017)
    - Sanford, Terry Jr.: Transcript, 1996 February 26 (Box 194)
    - Sanford, Terry on [Meredith?] College, undated (Box 182, Audio-cassette UA03600001-MCS-0019)
    - Sanford, Terry One Tape, 1995 27 December (Box 179, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0009)
    - Sanford, Terry Side A Only (Side 3 of 3) Tape #2, 1995 20 December (Box 179, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0011)
    - Sanford, Terry Tape #1, 1996 10 January (Box 179, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0007)
    - Sanford, Terry Tape #1, 1997 27 June (Box 179, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0002)
    - Sanford, Terry Tape #2, 1996 10 January (Box 179, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0008)
    - Sanford, Terry Tape 1 of 2, 1995 13 December (Box 179, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0012)
    - Sanford, Terry Tape 1 of 3, 1997 22 April (Box 179, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0004)
    - Sanford, Terry Tape 2 of 2, 1995 13 December (Box 179, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0013)
    - Sanford, Terry Tape 2 of 3, 1998 22 April (Box 179, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0005)
    - Sanford, Terry Tape 3 of 3, 1999 22 April (Box 179, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0006)
    - Sanford, Terry: Class, [?] 28 August (Box 179, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0022)
    - Sanford, Terry: Transcript, 1993 August 18-October 5 (Box 193)
    - Sanford, Terry: Transcript, 1993 January 14; 27 (Box 193)
    - Sanford, Terry: Transcript, 1993 November 16-December 29 (Box 193)
    - Sanford, Terry: Transcript, 1994 February 1-April 20 (Box 193)
    - Sanford, Terry: Transcript, 1995 December 13-27 (Box 193)
    - Sanford, Terry: Transcript, 1995 January 24 (Box 193)
    - Sanford, Terry: Transcript, 1995 March 17 (Box 193)
    - Sanford, Terry: Transcript, 1996 January 10 (Box 193)
    - Sanford, Terry: Transcript, 1997 April 22-June 26 (Box 193)
    - Sanford, Terry: Transcript, 1997 December 10-1998 March 24 (Box 193)
    - Sanford, Terry: Transcript, undated (Box 193)
    - Scheer, Johnan Tape 1, [?] 17 May (Box 179, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0017)
    - Scheer, Johnan Tape 2, [?] 17 May (Box 179, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0018)
    - Scott, Bob, 1998 7 May (Box 179, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0023)
    - Semans, Mary, 1995 11 September (Box 179, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0024)
    - Semans, Mary: Transcript, 1995 September 11 (Box 194)
    - Smith, Mac - McNeill Smith Tape 1 of 2, [?] 17 April (Box 179, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0032)
    - Smith, Mac Tape 2 of 2, [?] 17 April (Box 179, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0033)
    - Smith, Mac: Transcript, 1996 April 17 (Box 194)
    - Station, Bill: His Office Sanford, NC, 3-4:30pm, 1995 24 April (Box 179, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0021)
    - Staton, Bill: Transcript, 1995 April 24 (Box 194)
    - Terry Sanford Interviews with Mother, 1981-1982 (Box 194)
    - TL, [?] December 30 (Box 182, Audio-cassette UA03600001-MCS-0031)
    - Uick, Marsha, 1998 18 August (Box 179, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0016)
    - Wilder, Roy Reference Copy Tape 1 of 2, 1995 19 April (Box 180, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0070)
    - Wilder, Roy Reference Copy Tape 2 of 2, 1995 19 April (Box 180, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0071)
    - Wilder, Roy Tape #1, 1995 19 April (Box 179, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0014)
    - Wilder, Roy Tape #2, 1995 19 April (Box 179, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0015)
    - Wilder, Roy: Transcript, 1995 April 19 (Box 194)
    - Winters, John: His Office Raleigh, NC Tape 1 of 2, 1995 4 May (Box 179, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0034)
    - Winters, John: His Office Raleigh, NC Tape 2 of 2, 1995 4 May (Box 179, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0035)
    - Winters, John: Transcript, 1995 May 4 (Box 194)
  - Political Activity
    - End of Presidential Campaign, 1972-1980 (Box 184)
    - Gubernatorial Campaign Materials, 1960 (Box 184)
    - North Carolina Political Matters, 1958; 1964 (Box 184)
    - Presidential Campaign, 1969-1973 (Box 184)
    - Senate Campaign, 1986-1993 (Box 184)
  - Schedules and Planners
    - Executive Planner, 1970 (Box 187)
    - Executive Planner, 1971 (Box 187)
    - Executive Planner, 1973 (Box 187)
    - Executive Planner, 1974 (Box 188)
    - Executive Planner, 1975 (Box 188)
    - Executive Planner, 1976 (Box 188)
    - Executive Planner, 1977 (Box 188)
    - Executive Planner, 1978 (Box 188)
    - Executive Planner, 1979 (Box 189)
    - Executive Planner, 1980 (Box 189)
    - Executive Planner, 1981 (Box 189)
    - Executive Planner, 1982 (Box 189)
    - Executive Planner, 1983 (Box 189)
    - Schedules, 1996-1997 (Box 190)
  - Statements and Writings
    - Extra Sanford Speeches, 1977-1991; 2 folders (Box 185)
    - Statements and Writings, 1971; 1981; 1984; undated (Box 185)
    - Statements on Education, 1979-1981 (Box 186)
    - Storm Over The States, 1967 (Box 185)
    - Trip to China, 1980 (Box 186)
  - Subject Files
    - "To Terry Sanford" (book of letters honoring TS), 1985 (Box 187)
    - 1970s, 1964; 1970-1972; 2 folders (Box 186)
    - 1980s, 1984-1985 (Box 186)
    - 1985-, 1985-1998; 2 folders (Box 186)
    - Billy James Pettis, 1979 (Box 186)
    - Citizens Committee for Government Reorganization, 1971-1973 (Box 186)
    - Correspondence, 1971-1979 (Box 186)
    - Government Reorganization Committee, 1971 (Box 187)
    - National Defense, 1966 (Box 187)
    - Publications, 1981; 1997 (Box 187)
  - Terry Sanford Collection UNC-CH/SFC/FT93003 T-3531
    - T-.001, undated (Box 180, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0072)
    - T-.003, undated (Box 180, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0073)
    - T-.004, undated (Box 180, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0074)
    - T-.005, undated (Box 180, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0075)
    - T-.006, undated (Box 180, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0076)
    - T-.007, undated (Box 180, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0077)
    - T-.008 Tax Press KFC - 3160 - opens on 4/14 Tree Deal, undated (Box 180, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0078)
    - T-.010-012, .013 too damaged to re-record, .014 skipped, .015 (Terry Sanford Papers Re-recording project Tape #1), undated (Box 180, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0079)
    - T-.016-019 (Terry Sanford Papers Re-recording project Tape #2), undated (Box 180, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0080)
    - T-.020-024 Terry Sanford Papers (Tape Record Blank), undated (Box 182, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0167)
    - T-.021-023, undated (Box 180, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0081)
    - T-.024-027, undated (Box 180, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0082)
    - T-.028-032, undated (Box 180, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0083)
    - T-.033-037, undated (Box 180, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0084)
    - T-.036-038 Side 1: Blank (All other side) This side blank, Side 2: Tape is on this side, undated (Box 180, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0085)
    - T-.039-041, undated (Box 180, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0086)
    - T-.042-043, undated (Box 180, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0087)
    - T-.044 copy, 1961 21 September (Box 180, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0088)
    - T-.045 copy, 1961 28 September (Box 180, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0089)
    - T-.046 copy, 1961 29 September (Box 180, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0090)
    - T-.047 copy, 1961 5 October (Box 180, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0091)
    - T-.048 copy, 1961 11 October (Box 180, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0092)
    - T-.049 copy, 1961 19 October (Box 180, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0093)
    - T-.051 copy, 1961 2 November (Box 180, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0094)
    - T-.052 copy, 1961 10 November (Box 180, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0095)
    - T-.054 copy, 1961 16 November (Box 180, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0096)
    - T-.056 copy, 1961 29 November (Box 180, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0097)
    - T-.057 copy, 1961 5 December (Box 180, Audio-cassette UA03600001-CS-0098)